(ding)
- You don't want it, or who don't want it, right?
(upbeat music)
- Hello everyone, and welcome to Drop.
Has Alain the noticeings of Fish and Feedback show?
My name is James Harkin, I am joined by Dan Schreiber.
- Hello.
- Anatishinsky, and not Andrew Hunter Murray.
Your normal teacher is away.
- This is weird.
- Is it?
- It's hard.
- Do you feel like you're gonna be bullied all the way through?
- No way.
- Weirdly we bully the normal teachers,
and maybe the substitute teacher will show real respect.
- I'm like the headmaster, I've come in,
because your teacher has not been following the curriculum.
(laughing)
And I'm gonna start it all out, although I wish I might start it out,
but the truth is that Andy has put all of the emails
in one special place, and I will be going through his notes.
- Okay.
- So, dear Fisher, who is hosting in my absence.
Good luck, this is one of the most rewarding,
but difficult jobs in media, and I know you'll do a great job
in my absence, that's bullshit.
(laughing)
- Okay, we start with the get yourself off the hook.
- Oh, yes.
- Dr. Rowan J. DeFur writes in,
because we slandered yoga.
- Do you, I wasn't here for that.
- Dr. Rowan says, why you may, and indeed did,
write off the 3,000 year old practice as all that stuff.
(laughing)
- I think you should know that researchers show
in the modern yoga due to its holistic approach
to both mind and body can be effective
in the treatment of addiction, stress, depression, anxiety,
chronic pain, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
- I think always--
- To be emailing it bored of themselves at that point.
(laughing)
- I think what we said was that modern yoga
is based on modern things.
It's not really a massively historical,
especially the poses.
The poses were modern things that especially came
from Scandinavia and a few Indian texts.
I don't think we said anything that modern yoga
is not good for you.
- Yeah, I'm not sure we denied the effectiveness.
I know people whose lives are transformed by it.
- I remember when I first learned
that the Australian cricket team all did yoga,
and it was really helping them.
And it really annoyed me because at the time,
Molly O'Field, who's been on this podcast,
who's a good friend of us all,
I was working with her quite a lot and she does a lot of yoga.
And because one of my friends was doing it,
my head, it was like, oh, this is all bullshit.
- Right.
- But then finding out the proper sports people
and the Australian cricket team did it.
- Hey.
- Nice.
- Okay, there's a lot of adverts at the moment
because of the world cup on.
And Jordan Pickford is doing yoga ads on TV
at the moment.
- The England goalkeeper.
- Yeah, have you seen that?
- Yeah, I haven't seen that.
- It's like a yoga for goalkeepers
and he's pulling stretches on--
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm sorry, what can I buy?
- It's an app to teach you.
I think I didn't know this was gonna come up.
But--
- Yoga for goalies is a very neat thing
to be advertising, isn't it?
- I don't think that's the primary idea of the app,
because yeah, I think that's a limited market.
- Okay, here is another email from Stephen Garland,
subjects, Andy's tiny muscles.
- Okay.
- So do you remember we were talking
about Paul McCartney's eye muscles?
And Andy wanted to know what the smallest muscle
in his body was that he could train.
I suggested that maybe he could go to a bodybuilding competition
and with his stupidious muscle in his ear,
he could stretch it and they would go
from one millimeter to two millimeters.
And he would be a super strong man.
Well, Stephen says, "I hate to ruin the fantasy,
but even if you could train a muscle to make it longer,
brackets, you can't,
it wouldn't actually make it any stronger."
- Okay.
- That's because of muscle's maximum force,
it's determined by its cross-sectional area
and not its length.
- Yeah, all right, blah, blah.
- Body maxing is a thing that's going on right now.
Do you know the term body maxing?
- Is it like, 'cause I heard your episode with Jamie Martin,
you talked about ball maxing in that.
- It didn't mean that.
- His body maxing like a...
- I think it must be similar to that.
The idea is that every bit of your body
is something that you pay attention to.
So my friend the other day, his son was really depressed
because he's been trying to body max
this particular patch of his chest,
which is just by the shoulder.
- Okay.
- So if you just go inward from your shoulder
and he hasn't been able to tone it yet,
so body maxing is everything needs to get abs.
- This is no offense to your friend son,
but that is the saddest thing I've ever heard.
And it's running that epitomizes
solipsistic society today more than all,
I needed tone every single tiny fiber of body.
- What if that muscle is really important
for like changing light bulbs or something?
- Is that why he's doing it?
- He was living in the dark for years.
- There you go, don't be so rude.
- Anyway, I'm not, no, no, I think it's good to have friends.
- That friend is my dad and his son is me.
So screw you, buddy, screw you.
- So here's another one.
This is, get yourself off the hook for me, I think.
So this is from Holly Stratton.
And it refers to someone called Sewell Wright,
who was a genetics professor,
who was very into guinea pigs.
And I said that he was so into them
that once he kept a guinea pig under his armpit
and forgot it was there and picked it out
and used it as a board rubber.
- Yeah.
- Now you guys thought I was talking nonsense
because you couldn't possibly put a guinea pig
under your armpit and indeed--
- And forget it was there.
- Crucially.
- Well, no, I think Andy at least said
that I'd be walking around like some kind of weird muscle man.
- Because they can get big, yeah.
- But yeah, Holly says that she had the pleasure
of meeting Sewell Wright in 1980
when she was a young graduate student
in Wisconsin and he did not stash them under his armpits.
Give it a moment's thought, says Holly,
it's not believable.
And no, he never absentmindedly grabbed a guinea pig
to a razor-chop board.
It's a fun, apocryphal tale
and one we're all familiar with as genetic students,
but it isn't true.
- All familiar with.
It's sort of the most niche apocryphal tale.
- So I got this from a book called
a guinea pig's history of biology by Jim Endersby
and it was recounted by another student of Sewell Wright.
So I did have quite a good source for it.
And I think you can just keep a guinea pig under your arm
and I don't think you would be like this all the time.
- Well, if you were, it's a good hack for body-maxing.
Try to get it up my muscle-age
by just carrying that in the arm.
- Well, I have brought in.
- I don't have a guinea pig,
but I do have this fluffy haggis.
(laughing)
Splinky haggis.
What I thought is I would just keep it
under my armpit for the rest of the show.
- Yeah, go for it.
- Now I should say, for constituity reasons,
if we're going to cut this out,
I probably shouldn't do it.
Otherwise, I'm suddenly going to have a very ginger-herry thing
underneath my armpit.
But there you go.
- Okay.
- It's under there now.
I don't know if you can see that on the camera.
People watching.
- Well, you look buff as fuck.
(laughing)
- Like that's absolutely normal.
Like, are you going to wash that after this week's show?
- Absolutely not.
It goes straight into my daughter's bed
where it always lives, gorgeous.
- Absolutely, that's a great story.
- Like, I think you can hold your arm like this
and not exert too much pressure on it.
(laughing)
- Shut up.
- And it could live there perfectly happily.
- If that's a guinea pig that has scratched you to death,
now you've been torn up alive.
- Well, the story that I read about sewer writers
that he did it when the guinea pig's got a little bit
sort of fractious and they were running around too much
and he would kind of keep it quiet
by putting it under the armpit.
- That always calms me down, yeah.
Borrowed into someone's armpit.
- It's nice, I like it.
- Okay, well I'll take that out, shall I?
Just in case we cut it.
- Okay, next one, we have something from Bronwyn David
or David, but David I think.
- It's so smoothly.
This is what it could feel like all the time.
- Have you noticed that these are all things
that are actually related to the show?
- Yeah, we're learning, we're having fun.
- Are we having fun?
- I am.
- Good.
- I don't like to have fun and this is ideal for me.
- Okay, well, if you don't like to have fun,
you're gonna love this email from Bronwyn David
from Perth, Australia, who says that Anna posits
that the Australian eucalyptus trees in California
were of no use because the word was too soft.
That came as a surprise to me,
an Australian and granddaughter of a timber miller
who understood that eucalyptus is a hard word.
- Well, you know, be surprised.
- You know, I'm glad to have caught some surprise,
that's what we're here for, is to surprise people.
- The reason that eucalyptus trees in California
were not useful is because they were too young when cut
and the young word had an irregular grain
and it bent, cracked and shrunk when it tried.
- But young word or old word, it's always a hard word.
- I'm afraid so.
- On its dating profile.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- I think there's no way to get yourself off the hook there
'cause I googled it and it's definitely a hard word.
- I stand corrected.
I'm actually astonished in my current brain
that I ever claimed with certainty to know
what type of wood you could use as was
because I definitely don't know.
- Yeah, that's wild.
(laughing)
- Confidence.
- It just looks kind of squishy, what do you see it, you know?
- Yeah, I've got a eucalyptus tree in my house.
- Have you?
- Well, just outside my house, it's not mature
as in it's not a thick trunk or anything like that.
It's quite a skinny little thing, but it's quite cool.
- Does it have a name?
- Have a name too.
- I've had no quite a lot of trees in your house.
I've got names.
- Yeah, I've got a tree that I hug.
I'm called Daddy.
(laughing)
- I've blanked this out.
I think it was too strong.
- I had two until this moment.
- Did you also name one of the plants in your house?
- Yeah. - Baxter.
- Yeah.
- Baxter, he's in my office with me.
I say he, I don't know for certain.
- It'll be he and she, if it's a plant, I imagine.
- Yeah.
- You can't have male and female trees, don't write it yet.
(laughing)
Okay, bonus bream.
- Bonus bream.
You're on top of bonus bream.
- I'm not on top of any of them though.
They just washed right over me.
- I'm sure you have been flooded with emails about this,
says Finley Chope, but some buildings in Japan
have indeed installed emergency toilets.
- What's that in reference to?
- Toilets in lifts.
- Oh!
- Oh man.
- So many years ago, Andy did a fact on fish,
which was Japan is considering to install toilets
in its lifts, and we gave that fact to someone as a custodian,
and we wondered if they'd managed to do it,
and according to Finley they have,
and there's a Reddit where people talk about it,
and apparently when it's not being used as a toilet,
the lid allows it to be closed
and used as a seat for elderly passengers.
- That's very clever.
- I think I'd have to be feeling very rickety to sit on that toilet.
I don't know why.
- What's an emergency toilet?
You wouldn't be using it in any other facility.
- I mean, to sit on it as an elderly passenger
who didn't need a poo.
- Yes.
- Are you worried that if you sat on it
by accident with the lid open,
you would go through it and fall down the shaft?
- I think that's it.
- Oh wow.
- Yeah.
- The thing about being elderly, as I know,
is sometimes you don't think there's an emergency,
and then there's some liars in the emergency
of needing a poo so.
- Yeah.
- Anyway.
- Good night.
- Nice to have that little insight, thanks.
- Nice to have something to look forward to in a few years, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Dave Johnson says, "Hi, fish.
"I recently went to Puyda Foo."
- Hey! - Hey!
- Hey, no way.
- What they do, historical reenactment.
- Yeah.
And Dan, the show number slash times
for the seven main shows change each day,
and I only decided 24 to 48 hours in advance,
which is why they must need to print the timetable
and the map every single day.
- I'm sorry, but why?
When you've got a perfectly functioning thing,
is there some guy in HQ going,
"Let's mix it up again!"
(laughing)
"You, you're starting at seven!"
Like, why?
- Shuffle those cards.
Yeah, that's insane.
Is it because some people don't want to start at seven every day?
Is it like, you know, Zoe Bull probably wished
that she could only do the breakfast show one day or four at night,
but she stopped going at three a.m. every time.
- Perhaps you're a family and you're visiting,
and you can only visit between the times of 10, 30 and 11, 30,
and you don't want to always see the same thing.
- So do you think you can slip some money to the guy
who's doing the programming,
and that you can get your session early on the day?
- Sure, sure.
It's got to be a heavily corruptible system,
and I'm sure people are exploiting it.
- I tell you what, the hotel we just stayed in in Chenizia,
that's exactly what was going on.
Everyone was running their own racket.
There was a sun lounger racket with the guy
who was the life-safe guard at the pool.
You had to go to slip him 20,
and he would get you a sun lounger in the exact--
- For 20 quid?
- No, no, 20 Chinzian Connan with a currency's called.
- That could lead him to it.
- Yeah, it's not much when you break it down, but still--
- No, I think that's what's called a tip.
Someone's basically doing you a job,
and you just give them a little bit money on the side for--
- Kind of, but we got down there early one morning.
We put our stuff on the bench,
and the guy threw it off and put down the other person's.
'Cause you're not tipping him.
- Oh, it's disgusting.
- I already turned around, didn't it?
On your down, you thought that would be a relatable anecdote.
- It's bribery, I can't believe you.
- You know what, and I went to the kitchen,
I put my own burgers underneath the grill,
and they checked them out.
That's not what's happening here.
It's a sun lounger for everyone.
- Wait, but you put your towels down
and you went away for a while.
- Yeah.
- Right, so that's not a way you should be allowed
to save sun loungers.
And in fact, I think they've made that illegal.
I mean, I don't think you're gonna get arrested,
but haven't they had some German beaches
or on some beaches in Spain?
They've made it, that's not fair.
'Cause you can't just toss your towel on something,
and then say, all right, no one else allowed to sit
on it where we go.
- Well, it's how these hotels function.
You'll just be having no sun lounger for your entire trip.
- Well, it's good luck with that method.
- It's people like you, Dad, who are encouraging this method.
- No, with, I mean, whatever.
The whole thing's bullshit is what I'm trying to say.
- I would do, Anna, I just, every time I go on holiday,
I sit in the shade next to the toilet.
(laughing)
- 'Cause it's the only thing left.
Okay, we come to a new section,
which Andy has named, Fish Sticks.
Can you guess what that's about?
- Fish Sticks.
- Okay, well, fish dicks are made of just loads
of random different fishes mashed up together.
So is it miscellaneous?
- It is not, I would say that this should go
on the rodeo clown, because we have had quite a lot
of people writing in about drummers.
- Oh, okay.
- I see.
- And drums, because we said, what did we say?
Can you remember?
- Andy did a whole series of jokes.
What do you call a drummer who's, he basically suggested
that drummers were the useless people in a band.
I didn't want to get involved personally,
because I love drummers.
- And I don't think I did, but I think that explains
why Andy has gone holiday this week,
and left you to feel the correspondence about us.
- Oscar Marks Lewin says, "I study drums at university
and play in several bands, and I'm incredibly happy
with how drummers were represented in episode 639."
There are a few things I can look forward to more
in rehearsals than the lead guitarist,
handing me the iPad, so I can watch Coco Melon.
(laughing)
And then Oscar gives us a little bit
of extra information, which you guys will know,
but it is worth mentioning again,
'cause it's a brilliant fact, and it's about
the symbol manufacturers in the world.
Do you remember that fact?
- I mentioned that, I think, yeah.
- Yeah, it's the Avidis Zidjan company,
which is 403 years old, began in the Ottoman Empire,
and that family, including someone who got in an argument
that started their own company,
makes 80% of the world's symbols.
And I think they made them for the army originally,
didn't they, because when you're marching
and you're crashing your symbols.
- Yeah, it was an intimidation, so, as well,
during the Ottoman-- - But that's great fact.
- I think it's incredible.
- I absolutely love that.
Like it's insane that that was there,
and then it's on Ringo Star's drums.
That's just wild, what a beautiful journey.
- And this is the great thing about being a drummer,
you have the time to Google all of that sort of information
and email no such thing as a fish,
which is league guitarist.
You don't have--
- You're drumming with one hand and one foot,
and the other one, you're typing away.
- Yeah, very nice.
- Flores De Young gave us some nominative determinism
about drumming.
The drummer of avenged sevenfold, we all know and love.
And the former drummer of Bad Religion
is called Brooks Wachemann.
His brothers Chad Wachemann and John Wachemann
are also drummers.
- Brilliant.
- Wachemann's father Chuck, also a drummer,
taught them how to play drums.
- Very good.
- A whole family of Wachemann.
- That's wonderful.
I wasn't here for the Paul McCartney episode
that you guys did, but I sent Anna a fact,
which was after the Beatles, Paul McCartney
set up his own band, Wings,
and he auditioned a bunch of guitarists in the basement.
I think he was in New York,
and none of them knew who they were auditioning for,
but they rocked out.
The one he gave the job to,
and I feel this must be nominative determinism,
was a guitarist called Denny Lane.
(laughing)
The songwriter of Penny Lane picked Denny Lane
to be the guitarist in his band,
and that must have had a small influence on it.
- Yeah, wait, and this was pre-Penny Lane.
- No, this is off of Penny Lane.
- So, do we know that wasn't why he was chosen?
- No, he was chosen because he was a great guitarist.
- But do we know that it wasn't just the name?
- I think that's something that's been left unsaid.
- I think so, yeah.
- Everyone, too, is good to mention it.
- Yeah, sorry, I'm just going through my roller dex
of Beatles songs to think if there were any others
that could be named after people.
- Eleanor Rigby, but that already is.
- Eleanor Rigby.
- Denny Lane, you see, like Jenny Lane would be good.
- Yes, exactly.
There's no name that rhymes with yellow.
Is there for yellow submarine?
Would you want me to just listen some songs?
- Help.
- Help, guys.
- Howard, howard, days night, howard, howard.
- Howard days.
- Howard, anyway, beyond Lindstrom.
(laughing)
Beyond Lindstrom gives us another example
of a rodeo clown this week.
I wear a night cap, most nights.
- Okay.
- You remember this?
- How old is that?
- We were, we discussed and definitely no one wears
night caps anymore.
- No one wears night caps.
But then Andy said he really hopes some people
who wear night caps can write in with some photos.
And we have a photo here of Beyond wearing his night cap.
- Very nice.
- On his head.
- This was in the Nishkumar episode,
which you weren't in.
- Yeah.
- Damn, which is probably why you don't remember it,
but very politely not doing a long just in case,
it's something that we did say in an episode.
- Well, because the episode has gone out
and I didn't want to admit that I haven't listened to it yet,
so I've been faster now.
- Can I have another look at Beyond?
- Yeah.
- There you go.
- Is he, he looks like one of those,
yes, why is he wearing it like that over his eyes?
What are those toy elves that you get
that Sandy Tocksford once gave us?
- No, sir.
- The Nisha, which were their hats over their eyes.
- Well, let me tell you Anna, why he does that.
Because not only do they keep your head warm,
they can be pulled down over the eyes,
which works as like a sleep mask.
- Amazing.
Where did they come up with the technology for that?
- Well, do you know also that Lee writes in,
I don't know what Lisa name is,
and Lee says, if you pull the floppy triangular end
over your head and ear and put the tip under your arm,
you have three layers of fabric on the exposed side
of your head, which reduces sound,
so it can be used like an ear plug.
- Incredible, sir.
- And also, you can use the little bubble at the end
as a guinea pig if you've forgotten to bring
your underarm guinea pig that day.
- That's interesting, so you don't look buff on one side
and not the other.
- So there you are.
- Nightcups, very useful.
They can be used as I am asks and as earplugs.
And Bjorn says, there is a Swedish expression
at Tala in Natmorsen, which means to speak in the nightcap,
which means to talk through one's hat.
- Very nice.
- What does that mean, talk through your hat?
- Yeah, you need another clause there,
which is, which means to, that's so strange.
- Yeah.
- Bjorn says, yeah, as if that is a common saying in English.
He's talking through his hat.
- It must mean talk rubbish, right?
- Yeah.
- Or in secret, maybe if you wanted to share a secret
with someone, I don't need to lip read me.
I'll whisper it down behind my hat,
but that's behind my hat, not through it.
- I'm sorry, Bjorn, but that's not,
there might be a common expression
in the Andrew Hunter Murray house,
which is why Andy's included that in here,
but the three of us don't know it.
- Write in, if you know it,
all of Sweden, write into Andy next week.
- Okay, the next, oh, we're up to extreme fish.
I very much enjoyed your extreme fish,
amazing bit of graphics that you had last time.
- The interpretive dance.
- Yeah, but we won't be doing any of that today.
- Right.
(laughing)
- Because frankly, I think it's a bit over the top,
and I think Andy has been over the top for a long time now,
and it's about time he was rained in.
- You are the sort of strict teacher.
They did often do a line-in.
I enjoyed that answer.
Now, does anyone else have the real one?
- I didn't know what kind of substitute teacher you was gonna be.
If you're gonna be the kind of like, you know,
Shakespeare and hip-hop are actually, you know,
- Chair backwards.
- Hey guys, you don't need to call me Mr. Harkin.
Just call me James.
(laughing)
Jimmy Bob.
- No, I am not.
I'm the one who the real teacher has been taken away
for some unknown reason,
but there are rumors going around the school
as to why he's not in today.
And they involve Moss.
They involve Moss, and the headteach has come in
and realized that he's not been following
any of the proper rules.
- Yes.
- And he's coming in trying to keep the scores up
for the school.
- Well, you're in trouble with down on me.
(laughing)
- Libby Crawford writes in, says that she does seasonal work
in a forest in Sweden, and as well as listening
to an episode every night, she plays the podcast out loud
while she's working to keep the bears and moose away.
So another one of those.
- That's cool.
- When I'm in why bears and moose don't enjoy
no such thing as a fish?
- They don't, I'll go on there.
- No, we had an extreme fish
where someone was mountain hiking,
and if you play various voices,
bears don't like naturally to come to a group of people.
And so that's at least what we were told.
And so they were...
- Oh, 'cause you're disguising yourself as five people.
- Yes, exactly.
And James, you were saying recently
that you were in a bear-infested spot, weren't you?
- I was in Kosovo in the accursed mountains,
and they have bears there.
But the truth is that bears don't really
like hanging out where humans are.
- Yeah.
- So if you're walking on a normal trail,
they tend to not go near you.
And if you see one, you're pretty lucky.
In one respect.
(laughter)
And then when you're being torn apart,
that's where the unlucky bit comes in.
- It's six if one and half a dozen of the other, isn't it?
You're thinking it's your mother's death.
- But yeah, I saw very much in the distance,
a small brown pile of stuff that I wondered if it was a bear or not,
but then I took a photo, zoomed in,
took a photo, zoomed in.
And I couldn't tell what it was.
It might have just been a load of old rubbish.
- It would have been.
- But it was hard to tell.
- Bigfoot.
- You've got a photo of a big foot site.
- That's what I meant.
- Do they have those?
- I mean, you used to live in Kosovo.
- I did used to live in Kosovo for three months.
Does that count?
I think it does.
I'm not sure if they have their own Sasquatch.
They must do.
There must be a local, I guess.
- And all those places that have, you know,
that are in the wilderness,
they all have their cryptas, don't they?
- Yeah.
- Well, you should submit the picture to cryptid.com.
- Is there any podcast maybe that deals with this kind of thing?
- Yeah, you could, I could introduce you to me.
- Don't encourage it.
- The way I'm closed down.
- Libby has given us an extra fact.
And she says that the best thing I've read this week
is that ET is a little moist,
but he's dry when he's sick.
- ET is a little moist, but he's dry when he's sick.
Okay, the riddle.
- That's a riddle.
- No, it's just a fact.
- It sounds like a riddle, that can't be a fact.
- It was an interview with Steven Spielberg.
And he said that that's a biological fact about ET.
- I think so.
- Okay.
Is he ever sick in the film?
- Yeah.
- Well, that's Ellie.
- No, not just homesick.
- Oh, I thought he just missed so much.
- That's why he wanted to call.
- Is he?
- I didn't know it was about a dying alien.
- Well, no, and he gets better and then he gets sick again.
And yeah, there's a lot of things.
- Are you sure that was ET and not ER?
- That's George Clooney is in that one, yes, sorry.
- He was like, was it a childhood class?
- So, yeah, it got us a long movie.
Alright, I'll tune in next week with a fact.
- ET is a plant though, as was established in the sequel
of novelization of ET.
He's a botanist who lives on a green planet
and he himself is a plant species.
- Oh, wow.
- So moist, yeah, I guess you could if you've taken up water.
- Yeah, and then you plants do get sick of their too dry.
So this will actually make scientific sense.
- There we go.
- That's up.
- Okay, there we go.
Thank you, Libby.
We come to Andy's anecdote lounge.
Andy notes.
This is just a bit of calming midpoint of the episode.
So just put your feet up, relax,
and don't worry about anything.
- Midpoint.
- Yeah, I'm coming more worried now having other friends.
- I thought we were coming to the big closing.
- The last few pages are all section naming stuff
and people who are named after what they're now supposed
to be named after.
So we won't be doing those anyway.
- Excellent.
- Chuck 'n.
- Okay, we move on to Dr. Edwin Evelyn Ra,
right, re, reverse, age, twins.
- Oh, okay.
- Reverse, age, twins.
- What are we talking about that?
- This is to do with one of Andy's TV cop dramas.
- Oh, yes, right, yeah.
- And basically, Dr. Edwin has come up with a plotline
for our twin cop TV series.
For reverse, age, twins, imagine being pregnant with twins,
giving birth to the first child on, for example,
0, 0, 0, 1 on January the first.
That was one minute past midnight.
Next, we're time, Bada.
Then crossing over the Bada, back to the 31st of December,
the preceding year and birthing the second twin,
leading to the second child being born before the first.
Then when you die, leave a mysterious inheritance
to the older twin and let them fight it out.
- Okay, this is where the pitch gets good.
This is actually what Andy doesn't do.
He has the germ of the idea and then nothing comes of it,
but he's concluded it this person.
- This person, honestly, I think Dr. Edwin,
you need to go into like a team with Andy
with a two person writing team.
- Yes.
- I think in any two person writing team,
there's always one who basically doesn't do anything.
I just take two concepts, put some together,
gives it a title and then the other person does all of the work.
- Yeah, yeah, I hate those people, I hate them.
- Well, they'll be back next time.
- Damn it.
- And Dr. Edwin gives us one more bit
of nominative determinism.
They say that a surgeon they work with is called Dr. Soyan II.
- No.
- Really good.
- That is wonderful.
- Soyan II.
- It's really, really good.
- She didn't think this was nearly as interesting
or entertaining because I did.
So Dr. Edwin has gone up to this Dr. Soyan II
and said, you've got a funny name
and they've given them a short shrift.
Okay, we come to our final two pages of Andy's notes.
- Okay.
- Names, names, names.
Andy notes, there is really no need to go through these
in the episode.
I've already saved them separately
so they can go in the book.
(laughing)
- Okay, great, that's finished up.
- Lovely.
- Should we do a few anyway?
- Yeah, let's do some.
- Cool, Emily Stora, I bet you guys will remember this,
but we didn't think to put it in the book.
The aperiodic hat monotail is the Einstein tile.
So this is a shape that if you put them next to each other,
they test a light so you can fill up a whole space
with no gaps, but the pattern never repeats.
- Okay.
- And the known as Einstein tiles,
but they are not named after Albert Einstein.
They're named after the German for Einstein,
meaning one stone.
- Oh, that's quite nice.
- Oh, yeah, that's very nice.
- International Loving Day.
International Loving Day, Toby Cambrai tells us about that.
It was the day the US Supreme Court struck down
all anti-miskegenation laws.
Sorry if I've mispronounced that.
- I saidination.
- Yeah, I've never heard it said,
I've only seen it written down,
but it's banning mixed marriages.
- Okay.
- But it was named after Richard Loving.
- Oh, that's cool.
- With his wife, Mildred Jester sued the state of Virginia,
where they were exiled after marrying good stuff.
- Oh, Alma Loving.
- Alma Loving.
Alma Loving, Beatles.
- Well done, there you go.
- Very nice.
The Alex Keck Park Memorial Garden.
Max Avery writes him with this one.
This is a memorial garden inside a park
called Alice Keck Park,
and the woman's actual name was Alice Keck Park.
- Lovely.
Alice Keck Park.
- So it's not to do with actual parks,
and it's not to do with kecking yourself.
- No.
- Because I wouldn't go to a park that had keck in the name.
I think it was full of shit.
- Is that what it means, keck?
- For me, keck your pants.
- I call kecks trousers.
- Or I call trousers.
- Keck your pants.
Sorry, you keck your kecks.
- If there's one thing listener you've learned
from this episode is that you keck your kecks,
you don't keck your kecks.
- Don't keck your kecks, yeah.
- Dean Blackwell was listening to episode 397
when we were talking about rugby,
and we mentioned two newspapers
who blunderingly referred to two individuals
who played hucker as prostitutes at the halls.
As a Kiwi, I actually loathe rugby.
However, it may excite you to know
that the all Blacks hucker from 2002 to 2013
was called Andrew Hall.
- Oh, that's very good.
- I don't know if it was some sort of weird AI
that confused Hucker with a hole.
- I think it was, yeah.
- Got it.
Like that, this was like way before the days of AI
when there was that article about Tyson Gay,
who was a basketballer.
- Sprinter.
- Exactly, a sprinter, as I was saying,
and there was a big article about him
which referred to him all the way through
as Tyson Homosexual.
Do you remember?
And this was like 15 years ago,
so I don't know what weird automated system they were using,
but it wasn't advanced.
Finally, we have some ideas for Andy's buck.
- Okay.
Basically, we're trying to look for a more catchy name,
a catchy title for things which you think would be named
for one reason because the name is related to that reason,
whereas in actual fact, they are named for the name of a person
or thing that is not related to that reason,
but is opposite for some reason.
- Yeah, and I've said it before, that's the perfect title.
So I don't know why we're even in this.
- Yours was actually even better than Andy's.
I've gotta say, I liked it.
- Well, Jack Reeves' air suggests that we call them
humorous misnomas, names, not because they are humorous,
because of course they are, says Jack, I would disagree.
But after Andrew, you to Murray.
- Oh my God.
- Come out.
- Good bye.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Thank you everyone.
(laughing)
- Thank you.
- Okay, well, I think we should use that opportunity to wrap up.
(laughing)
- Someone actually typed that.
Someone actually told us worth five minutes of my time
to sit down and type this out.
- Christ.
- Thanks for writing it.
- No, please writing again.
But no, do something else with your life.
- No, thank you so much, Jack, for writing in.
- We're joking.
- And thank you everyone who's written in,
please continue writing into us at podcast@QI.com.
That is where Andy collects all of your stuff
and sends it out to us for little fish if it's a fact,
or keeps it for himself if he wants to use it
in droppers of line.
I've been James Harkin.
These two have been Dan Shriver and Anna Toshinsky.
We'll be back in two more weeks with Andy back here.
So if you're missing all of his nonsense,
all of his shenanigans,
and you didn't like your supply teacher,
then don't worry, he will be back.
I believe all the charges against him have been dropped.
And we will see you again in two weeks.
Good bye.
Now that's how you do an outro.
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]